Brandon Bledsoe

12113 Metric Boulevard • Austin, TX 78758
Phone: (832) 312-6687 • E-Mail: brbledsoe.m@gmail.com



Summary

Experienced childcare provider, have worked with children ranging in age from 5 to 12 years old. Caring, patient, and capable of adapting to all situations. Knowledge of any outdoor recreational activity, and sport. Broad base of different experiences and jobs.

Experience

After School Daycare Assistant

August 2009 - June 2010 | Spring, TX

Planned and monitored activities for K – 5th grade students after school. Helped students with homework. <u>Campus Kids LLC</u> (campuskidsllc.com)

Account Manager

March 2013 - May 2014 | Houston, TX

Met with oil & gas operators to understand their needs, organize how TanMar can meet those needs, and produce sales for TanMar as a result.

<u>TanMar Companies LLC</u> (tanmarcompanies.com)

Hunting Guide/Ranch Hand

Summers of 2003-2007 | King Ranch

Guide clients on hunting and fishing trips. Help clear a system of hunting trails on the ranch for clients. Rancho Tio Moya (tio moya ranch – Google Search)

Education

Lone Star College System

Courses Include: All Basics, Some Business & Economic classes.

Skills

*Serving Others *Working w Children

For more info visit my LinkedIn page (http://www.linkedin.com/pub/brandon-bledsoe/99/710/b21)